Christian Paranas

Tacloban, Eastern Visayas, Philippines



dev.christianparanas@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/christianparanas



09169437066



https://christianparanas.me

Summary

I'm Christian Paranas an entry-level web developer currently living in Tacloban city, Philippines. I specialize in building websites and desktop applications. My current toolset includes Angular, React, Node, SequelizeORM, and other various frameworks, libraries, and technologies related to them.

Experience



Web Developer

Freelance

Mar 2020 - Present (2 years 1 month +)

M Service Crew

McDonald's

Aug 2018 - Nov 2019 (1 year 4 months)

Education



Eastern Visayas State University

Bachelor's degree, Information Technology 2018 - 2023

Northridge Institute of Business and Technology Inc.

Creative Web Design Dec 2020 - Jan 2021

Skills

HTML5 • React.is • Angular • Git • SASS • Node.is • Laravel • MySQL • Shopify • WordPress